

 $\searrow$ 

arifawais328@gmail.com



03446896054



Islamabad, Pakistan



linkedin.com/in/awais-arif-410152228



github.com/Awais-Arif

#### **SKILLS**

нтмі

CSS

BOOTSTRAP

**JAVASCRIPT** 

**TYPESCRIPT** 

REACT JS

ANGULAR

API INTEGRATION

# **LANGUAGES**

Urdu

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

English

Full Professional Proficiency

#### **INTERESTS**

Literature

Cricket

Reading

Writing

# Awais Arif

Frontend Developer

Awais Arif, a professional Frontend Developer with over 1 year of experience. I am an expert in developing high-quality, user-friendly, and responsive website applications and React components. My area of expertise is React and Angular.

#### **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR'S IN COMPUTER SCIENCE (BCS)
COMSATS UNIVERSITY ISLAMABAD

02/2018 - 02/2022

INTERMEDIATE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE (ICS)
PUNJAB COLLEGE BHARA KAHU

04/2015 - 04/2017

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Front End Developer (Angular)
Jezzba

03/2022 - Present

## **ORGANIZATIONS**

CSS CUI (06/2019 - 02/2022)

Content Writer

IEEE CUI (05/2019 - 02/2022)

Content Writer

### **CERTIFICATES**

UDEMY (01/2021 - 03/2021)

FreeCodeCamp (06/2021 - 09/2021)

#### PERSONAL PROJECTS

Angular App (03/2022 - Present)

□ TECHNOLOGY - ANGULAR

Team Generator

□ TECHNOLOGY - ANGULAR

Hangman

□ TECHNOLOGY - REACTJS

iDoctor

□ TECHNOLOGY - REACTJS

Smart Society Application (02/2021 - 02/2022)

□ TECHNOLOGY - REACT NATIVE

YouTube Clone

□ TECHNOLOGY - HTML, CSS